Md. Asaduzzaman (Aminur)

Full Stack Developer (Laravel, VueJS)

Github: github.com/aminur670 Website: aminur670.github.io Mobile: +88 01719 670601

E-mail: aminur670601@gmail.com

Address: Komaygari, Naogaon Sadar, Naogaon-6500.



Career Objective

Willing to Build Up Career in A Challenging Position and To Prove Myself as A Quick Learner and Highly Energetic Person to Face Any Challenge in The Computer Sector Where the Contribution Will Be Acknowledge, If Would Be Given an Opportunity. To gain a position of a programmer in a software company that can provide me an opportunity to work on several projects for writing, testing, and debugging code.

Career Summary

Excellent skill & motivate in computer professional with more than 2 years' experience in the IT field. Gather highly knowledge about programming field, and Technical Support with successful implementation of it. Have good understanding knowledge of Python Object Oriented Programming Language, Hardware/Software Installation and Configuration.

Employment History

Years of Employment Experience: 2+ Years

✓ Assistant Web Developer (Jan, 2021 - Aug, 2021):

Faith Media LTD.

Location: 29th Street, Mohakhali DOHS, Dhaka.

Department: Web Design & Development, IT

Duties/Responsibilities:

- Making WordPress sites with Elementor as approved design as client requirement
- ✓ Making Project plans for team workflow
- ✓ Developing Website/Web Application & UML/Features Models as client requirement
- ✓ Products Data/Image upload & update to eCommerce website
- ✓ Product Image Retouch & Editing, Product Listing,

✓ Virtual Office Assistant (Jan, 2020 - Dec, 2021):

Remote Job

TIC Accessories LTD.

Location: 167th Street, Jamaica, New York 11432, USA.

Department: Ecommerce Site Duties/Responsibilities:

- ✓ Promotional Email Template Creating for products
- ✓ Sending Emails, Email Marketing with provided mailing list
- ✓ E-Commerce Site Managing, Product Listing, Shipping,
- ✓ Finding e-commerce site's issue & notify to developers
- ✓ Collecting Products info & visuals
- ✓ Photo Editing, PDF Editing, Document Making, Workforce Planning
- ✓ Operating system & Softwares installation & configuration, Software troubleshooting as needed.





✓ IT Trainer & ICT Teacher (Jul, 2019 - Dec, 2020):

EEE & IT Engineering Training Center

Location: Mondol Mor, Sapahar-6560, Naogaon, Rajshahi.

Department: ICT & IT (SSC & HSC)

Duties/Responsibilities:

- √ Taking classes:
 - ➤ Programming Basic256 (for Kids of 6-8th Class), C/C++ & OOP, Python & OOP
 - ▶ Basics of HTML, CSS, JS, PHP, Database, etc.
- ✓ Perform theory & practical classes.
- ✓ Making presentation for interactive classes.
- ✓ Maintain and addressing about IT related issue.

Employment & Projects Experience

Employment: 2+ years of experience in IT Sector

- 1. EEE & IT Training Center (ICT Teacher)
 Jul,2019 Dec,2020 >> 6 months
- 2. TIC Accessories Ltd (Virtual Office Assistant)
 Jan,2020 Dec,2021 >> 1 year
- 3. Faith Media Ltd (Assistant Developer)
 Jan,2021 Aug,2021 >> 6+ months

Projects: Worked in 5+ Projects

- 1. ChemByNavid.com (Online Education)
- 2. GontobboXpress.com (Delivery System)
- 3. RealCafeBD.com (Company Site)
- 4. DifferentCafeBd.com (Company Site)
- 5. FaithMediaLtd.com (Agency Site)
- 6. Tholay.xyz (Products Image & Listing)
- 7. Rongtuli.com (Products Image Listing)

Academic Qualification						
Exam Title & Major Subject	Institute	Result	Year	Duration		
Diploma in Engineering, Computer Technology	Bogura Polytechnic Institute, Bogura	2.92 out of 4	2017	4 Years		
S.S.C. (Voc) Computer Department	Naogaon Technical School & Collage, Naogaon-6500	4.88 out of 5	2013	2 Years		

Professional Training Summary						
Training Title	Institute	Location	Year	Duration		
Web Design & Development	Bangladesh IT Institute	Parbota, Mirpur-10,	2017	3 Months		
	(BITI)	Dhaka-1216				

Independent Professional Training Summary						
Independent Professional Training Title	Course Time	Completing Year	Duration			
C/C++ Programming Language	07-12-2016 to 1-06-2016	2016	6 Months			
Linux Operating System	01-01-2016 to 1-06-2017	2016	6 Months			
Web Design & Development	05-06-2017 to 06-12-2017	2017	6 Months			
WordPress (Elementor + Plugin)	03-01-2018 to 20-06-2018	2018	6 Months			
Laravel	06-06-2020 to 12-01-2021	2021	6 Months			
VueJS	25-01-2021 to 15-06-2021	2021	6 Months			



Programming & Skills

- √ C/C++, Python, PHP, JavaScript, SQL
- ✓ HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, jQuery
- ✓ Laravel, Inertia, VueJS, Axios, API, REST, Git, Node,
- ✓ SQLite, MySQL, MongoDB Database
- ✓ WordPress Customization with Elementor & plugins
- ✓ Using Experience: 6+ Windows Distro, 10+ Linux Distro, C-Panel & Hosting System
- ✓ Adobe Photoshop & Illustrator, SimpleMind, VS Code, Github, Trello, Google Sheet
- ✓ Software & Hardware Problem Solving.
- ✓ Office Assistance, Internet Browsing, Emailing, Letter/Documents Typing (Bangla & English)
- ✓ Microsoft Office 2016 (Word, PowerPoint, Excel, Outlook)

Language Proficiency

✓ Fluent in reading, writing, speaking and understanding in both Bangla and English.

Activities and interests

- ✓ Good knowledge in programming languages (OOP & Procedural)
- ✓ Career oriented, hardworking and ability to handle multiple tasks
- ✓ Quick learner and ability to learn new concepts
- ✓ Pivotal Cloud Foundry Platform (GitHub)
- ✓ Strong collaboration skills
- ✓ Excellent communication skills

Achievements

✓ Strong communication and interpersonal skills.

: 19976426001000186

National ID

- ✓ Good analytical and problem-solving skills.
- ✓ Good Skill on Software Development across Platforms & Operation Systems.

Personal Strengths

- ✓ Highly motivated, self-disciplined, good team organizer, and pleasantly adaptable.
- ✓ Always keen to take on responsibility and possess strong leadership qualities.
- ✓ Work under pressure at a fast pace and committed to professionalism.

Personal Information

Name : Md. Asaduzzaman (Aminur) : Md. Abul Kalam Azad : Md. Abul K

Mother : Mst. Anju Ara Post : Naogaon Sadar.
Birth Date : 22/01/1997 District: Naogaon-6500.
Gender : Male Division: Rajshahi.
Height : 5'9"

Religion : Islam <u>Present Address</u>
Nationality : Bangladeshi (By Birth) Same as Permanent Address

Contacts

Mobile: 01719-670601 Github: github.com/aminur670 Email: aminur670601@gmail.com Website: aminur670.github.io

Reference

✓ Reference 01

Name: Md. Azizul Aman Al Amin

Organization: Bogura Polytechnic Institute,

Bogura

Designation: Chief Instructor and Head of

Department (Computer Technology)

Mobile: +88 01712685203

Email: amanrajshahi@yahoo.com

✓ Reference 02

Eng. Mohammad Ali (Jr. Instructor)

Computer Technology

Bogra Polytechnic Institute, Bogra.

Cell: +8801712-710603